thiscaller.com 2016-03-24

# Home - ThisCaller.com

### Privacy Policy

* * *

#### Personal Information ThisCaller.com Collects

You may use ThisCaller.com without creating an account. Even without an account, ThisCaller.com collects information about Your use of ThisCaller.com. This may include information about any IP address used to access ThisCaller.com and Your activity on ThisCaller.com. ThisCaller.com uses cookies, or small text files stored on Your computer, to store data about Your visits.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs);  
\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you);  
\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);  
\- To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers' hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Children�s Privacy

ThisCaller.com is directed to people who are at least 18 years old, and ThisCaller.com does not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. If You are aware that ThisCaller.com has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of 18, please alert ThisCaller.com at [Contact Page](http://www.thiscaller.com/contact) and the information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible. This policy regarding collection of data from children exceeds the requirements of the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Removing your Personal Information from ThisCaller.com

You may remove your information from the ThisCaller.com phone directory, please contact us via [Contact Page](http://www.thiscaller.com/contact), your information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible.  
For any suggestions and comments regarding ThisCaller.com or our Privacy Policy, please contact us via [Contact Page](http://www.thiscaller.com/contact).  
If you feel this website does not comply with any of the above stated Privacy Policy terms or if you have any questions you can [Contact Us](http://www.thiscaller.com/contact).
